It's time to rise
Just hand over the mic
It's our turn to shine
We don't waste no time
You can try but you can never dim our lights
Let me take you on a little walk down history
Tragedies, blood sweat & tears for this victory
I'd be lying if I said that it was easy
My people barely breathing
A world without humanity
Rice field full of casualties (Rice field full of casualties)
Tapestry of travesty but
We're over all the agony
We're taking back our sanity
So feel our rising majesty
ចាបុីដងវែង ល្ខោនបាសាក់
សិល្បៈអាយ៉ៃ ចាបុី
We won't forget, said we won't forget
ផ្លាស់តាមពេលតាមសម័យក្មួយចេះរៀបចំឲ្យសមប្រពៃ
We'll try our best, លោកតា, we'll try our best
I wanna know អ្នកណាសាទរពេលដែលឃើញយើងថ្កើន
We're ready to go, we in control, I'm ready to fight so tell me the time
I said time to rise ពេលវេលាមានតម្លៃទៅឲ្យខ្ពស់ហួសចម្ងាយ
ដូចលោកគ្រូ ណៃ រះឲ្យខ្ពស់ហួសពីផ្កាយ
ធ្វើឲ្យអស់ដៃមិនឆិនឆៃតែឆើតឆាយ
​I said time to rise ភ្លឺដូចជាថ្ងៃមានចម្ងាយរាប់លានម៉ាយល៍
គិតដូចបណ្ឌិតមានគំនិតដូចចៅ ហ្វាយ
រីកដូចជាផ្សិត​ ខួរខ្ញុំគិត ដៃខ្ញុំកាយ
They tryna break my soul
តែខ្ញុំឆ្អិនដល់បណ្ដូល
លុយគេអ្នកជះខ្ញុំអ្នកប្រមូល
ខ្ញុំប្រមូលដូចកុងត្រូល
They might lose control
ព្រោះពីមុនដូចកន្ទបតែឥឡូវដូចជាហូល
បុរាណលាយសម័យលាយឲ្យចូល
ទាញជាកម្រៃ ច្នៃវាចូលដូចចំណូល
ខ្ញុំសូមរៀបរាប់ ជម្រាបសណ្ដានឲ្យបានដឹង
កុំនូវស្ងៀមត្រឹង បាត់ឈឹង អញ្ចឹងត្រូវប្រឹងរឹងបុឹង
ព្រោះមានរឿងជាច្រើនដែលអ្នកមិនដឹង
អ្នកណាស្នងតំណែង បើឯងអញ្ចឹង?
កុំធ្វើជាសំណែននៅលើហឹង
បើគេមិនឲ្យតម្លៃរត់ចូលព្រៃធ្វើជាសិង្ហ
បើចូលទឹកដូចក្រពើ នៅលើឈើធ្វើជាជ្រឹង
PULL UP